Jake, hurry up, I'm starving.
Sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I just had to grab my waaaalleeeet...
Gentlemen.
Fine, I was trying something,
and it didn't work!
Okay, before we get going,
Sgt. Jeffords has suggested
that it would improve morale
if we started the meeting
with some consensual non-work jabber.
I just said it might
be nice if you checked in
on the squad's personal
lives every now and then.
Exactly, jabber. Scully, go.
Well, it was just a
regular morning for me.
Woke up again with my
dog's butt on my mouth.
This experiment has failed.
Back to work talk.
Peralta, I have a case for you.
- Uh, that's a no-can-do, sir.
- Excuse me?
Oh. Sorry. I didn't mean to come
across like a rabble-rouser.
We're just simply unavail.
We have a meeting at a new multi-agency,
multi-state task force.
- It's a double multi.
- It's a multi-multi.
You're better at everything than I am.
- Don't say that.
- It is what it is.
They're taking down a street racing gang
that's been using souped-up cars
to transport drugs across state lines.
It's a real-life
"Fast and the Furious" movie.
Don't those movies glorify lawlessness?
No. They glorify family and loyalty
and big, hard boobs on
both men and women.
And guess who's heading
up the task force?
Sgt. Boomer Maxwell!
- Oh!
- Damn!
Boomer Maxwell? What
kind of name is that?
Is he a football player and/or Rugrat?
Dude, he's an NYPD legend.
I heard he took down three
serial killers in one week.
I heard he defused a bomb with his teeth
because his hands were tied up.
I heard he bangs constantly.
Hitchcock, no chime-ins for you.
Well, good luck. I know how
competitive these task forces can be.
Especially this one.
Because Boomer's amazing.
- In bed.
- Come on, Hitchcock!
Oh, hey! What are you doing down here?
Upstairs bathroom's broken
I think Scully did it.
He says he hasn't been
in the women's bathroom,
but who else would leave a whole
rotisserie chicken in there?
Did you ask Gina to submit a work order?
Yes, but she hasn't done it yet.
She views doing her job
as quote unquote optional.
Well, I'm glad it's broken,
'cause it's nice to see you.
Now, get in that stall
and kill it in there.
- What?
- Sorry. I'm a manager now,
so I'm trying to be more motivational.
Oh! So it's totally cool for detectives
to come down here and take
dumps in our bathroom?
Excuse me, Officer,
you need to check your tone.
Sorry, Sarge, but we're all sick
of detectives looking down on us.
I bet you don't even
know my name, Rosa Diaz.
Okay, look.
I get that there's always been tension
between uniformed
officers and detectives,
but Rosa is one of the good guys.
I'm sure she knows your name.
You clearly just texted her the answer.
No, she didn't. Della Avocado.
- It's Alvarado.
- Stupid auto-correct.
I knew you were still one of them.
We all knew.
Great.
Now I'm caught in a turf war
between my new squad and my old squad.
I know this is a big
deal for you as a manager,
but I gotta pee real bad.
Right. Right, right, right.
I believe in you.
Teach that toilet a lesson!
Oh, my God.
These guys are the best of the best.
- What, are you nervous?
- Yeah! Very. You?
I mean, I was, but then I looked
at Boomer's personnel file.
We both started in the same precinct,
we both took down drug gangs
our first year as detectives,
and we've both been
referred to as... El Ganador.
Oh, that's weird. I've never
heard anyone calling you that.
Well, they will soon. The point is,
I'm basically a young Boomer Maxwell.
Oh, you guys didn't hear?
Boomer's not running the
special unit anymore.
He shattered both his legs
jumping off the Chrysler Building
onto a passing garbage
truck during a chase.
Damn, that is so cool.
They say he'll never walk again.
Oh. Well, that's very sad.
But also still cool.
He's gonna be an Ironside!
Wait, if Boomer's not doing it,
who's running the task force?
Detective Brett Booth from 6-3.
- Oh! Cool, cool, cool.
- Uh-oh.
That was your worried
"cool, cool, cool."
- Who's Brett Booth?
- We were in the academy together.
During a training exercise,
I shot him with a rubber bullet
and somehow it got underneath his
goggles and hit him in the eye.
It kind of messed up
his depth perception.
Oh, but that was a long time ago.
I'm sure he's totally fine now
and he's forgotten all about it.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Jake Peralta, my old...
Rogers!
It happened again!
I told you to keep the walkways clear!
You're gonna regret this, Peralta!
Ah!
Stupid Brett Booth not letting us
on his task force.
Just because you blinded him in one eye.
His other one works just fine.
No, I mean, the water cooler
thing was pretty bad.
- Yeah, he can't see.
- You know what, screw this.
We don't need a task
force to work the case.
All we have to do is solve
it before Booth is done
with his interviews in two days.
- That's impossible!
- You know I hate the word "impossible"
unless it's immediately followed
by the words "Ghost" and "Protocol."
- Shh.
- Be advised.
We have a shooting or something
- going on in Brooklyn Heights.
- What's going on?
There's an active shooter in
a hotel in Brooklyn Heights.
Requesting additional units,
squad dispatch.
Multiple casualties.
ESU is en route, and nearby officers
are responding to the scene right now.
We have people running. Advising
six or seven shots fired.
Numerous civilians coming this way.
Warwick, 9238, show me going.
9238, I have you going.
Hilbert, 9825, show me going.
- 9825, I have you going.
- What are they saying?
"Show me going" and their badge number.
They're telling dispatch that they're
close by and they're responding.
Diaz, 3118, show me going.
Diaz? Rosa Diaz?
That's her badge number.
Rosa's there.
So there's limited information about
the situation in Brooklyn Heights,
but I did manage to speak
to a captain at the 9-7,
- who offered an update.
- Do we know how many shooters?
Two, possibly three.
Again, the situation's still developing,
but as of now, there are three dead
and multiple wounded, all civilians.
So we're going up there, right?
To help Rosa?
ESU is on the scene,
and the 9-7 is locking down the area.
It's already a zoo.
They wanted us to remain on alert
- but not to respond.
- Yeah, but that's just a suggestion,
like how they tell you to drink
eight cups of water every month.
- A day.
- Sarge, come on.
- This is not the time for jokes.
- No, it wasn't a suggestion.
We've been ordered to go
about our business as usual.
I know you're all concerned about Rosa,
but she's not going in alone.
She's part of a massive NYPD response.
And it's Rosa, right?
I mean, she's a badass.
She's the toughest of all of us.
No offense, guys.
- No, that's accurate.
- Very fair.
I could take her. What? I'm wily.
I promise you, I will keep you updated
if I learn anything.
In the meantime, you all
have jobs to do. Dismissed.
Ames. She's gonna be okay.
I know.
- I love you.
- Love you too.
Are you done trying
to get into Amy's pants?
- What?
- I'm sorry. I'm freaking out.
Look, I'm worried too,
but spiraling isn't gonna help anything.
We can't go up there,
so the best thing we can do
- is try not to think about it.
- How are supposed to do that?
Well, it's called compartmentalizing.
Not to brag, but when you
come from a broken home,
you get pretty good at it.
It's like, "Hey, whose bra is that
in the back seat of my dad's car?
I'm sure it just blew
in there on accident.
Anyways, off to third grade!"
I can't. I dwell on everything.
I'm a dweller. I wake up every morning,
I'm worrying about the Zika virus.
Why is nobody talking
about Zika anymore?
There's no way it fixed!
Okay, look. We'll just ignore
what's going on together.
Okay? Let's focus on the case.
Let's become... street racers.
Okay, Charles.
How do I look?
So cool. How do I look?
Uh... you definitely made a choice.
- You almost look like...
- Speed Racer?
Right? This is exactly what he wears!
And the best part is...
I can use the kerchief
to start the race!
Well, I wanted this op to
feel normal, and... it does.
This is quintessential Charles.
Okay. Let's go over
the backstories. I can start.
Actually, it's maybe
better for me to go first
so you can make some internal edits
before you say yours out loud.
- Perfect. After you.
- Great.
My name is Axel Richards.
I've been driving stolen cars
since I was six years old.
- Wow, that's young.
- Oh, yeah.
I had to use a Wiffle Ball bat
to just reach the gas pedal,
and I never learned to use the brakes.
- That sounds so dangerous.
- Not if you know what you're doing.
- Great response.
- Thank you.
Anyways, things went south
when I got addicted to drugs
after my best friend died in
an active shooter situation.
Oh, I see what I did there.
Hey. What are you doing in here?
Holt's scanner was making me anxious,
so I came in here to listen
to some calming music.
It's me singing the song I wrote.
♪ Subway girl ♪
♪ Gettin' all the looks ♪
♪ Holdin' onto your ♪
♪ Big pile of books, yeah ♪
Listen. I was thinking,
Rosa seemed pretty annoyed
about the broken toilet up here,
and since she's having a rough day,
I thought it would be nice
if we got it fixed for
her before she got back.
And you came to me
'cause I'm the only one
who ever gets anything done around here.
And because you were supposed
to get it fixed last week,
so it's kind of a second chance for you.
This is a time of crisis,
so we're supposed to be
lifting each other up.
Why don't you call that plumber
I've been asking you to call
for a few hours now?
All units, hold your positions.
Any news, Sergeant?
Uh, last I heard,
they've located one shooter,
but they can't get to him.
Oh, I'm sorry, I didn't realize
you were on the phone.
Oh, just on hold. What's up?
I just wanted to check in
to see if you were all right.
I couldn't help but notice that
you've flattened your mouse.
Sorry. I get crushy when I'm nervous.
If there's anything you want to
talk about, my door is always open.
Metaphorically.
In reality, I often keep my door closed,
for privacy, security,
climate control...
You know what, I never even
should've used a metaphor.
I'm better than that.
If there's anything you
want to talk about,
please do so now.
There is.
I'm so scared for Rosa.
And I realized, I haven't looked at
my life insurance policy
since Ava was born.
I'm on hold with them now.
Terry needs a bulkier plan!
Look, I get that you're worried
about your own mortality.
Perhaps this fact will comfort you.
As an NYPD officer,
you're more likely to be
crushed by scaffolding
than to die on the job.
Oh, God.
This is a city of scaffolding!
No, no, Sergeant,
I was only trying to point out
that there are millions
of potential ways to die.
Do you know how common choking is?
What are you doing, man?
Yeah, so this won't be a problem.
I can pencil you in tomorrow.
Oh. Uh, we kind of need you to fix it
before our friend gets back today.
I'm sorry, it's gonna take a while,
and I have other appointments.
Well, can you cancel them?
I didn't want to do this,
but our friend is a cop,
and she's caught in a Brooklyn
Heights shooting right now.
Oh! So you think you're the first people
that ever needed a toilet fixed
'cause a loved one's life was in danger.
- Yes?
- You're not. Welcome to New York.
That's a grim commentary
on the city we live in.
Refresh. No news. Refresh. No news.
Why is there no news?
- Charles, come on.
- Compartmentalize, remember?
Try and think happy thoughts
like the Shrek musical.
Come on, Jake,
you know they shut that down.
The health board said there
was too much mud on the stage!
Yeah, probably for the best.
All right, that didn't work.
How about this? Let's
clean up our desks.
Right? That's always
good for a distraction.
Oh, no. Rosa gave me this notepad.
I remember I was all,
"Anyone got a notepad?"
And she said, "Yep, here."
- Oh, my God, that's so Rosa.
- I know.
Okay. So, before you
can change a policy,
I'm gonna have to ask you
a few medical questions,
- check your vitals.
- Great. Just do it fast.
- Terry knows tomorrow's not promised.
- Okay.
Then let's start with
your blood pressure.
We can skip this part.
I always clock in at 130 over 80.
Terry's in tiptop.
Shots fired. Shots fired!
- What?
- Is anybody hurt?
- I don't know.
- Oh, man.
And your BP's at 290. Oh, 350.
- You broke the machine.
- All right, screw this.
There were shots fired.
I just got off the phone.
There are two officers down.
Neither one of them is Diaz.
So what, are we supposed
to wait until one is?
Sir, we have to go up there.
We have to help Rosa.
ESU has more than enough manpower,
and we have been ordered to stay in
this precinct by the commissioner.
So what? He's not a part of our squad.
He doesn't care about her.
Look, I know you're concerned
about Diaz, as am I.
Nevertheless, I am ordering
you to stay in this precinct.
Fine.
I understand that's your order.
- What'd he say?
- Doesn't matter.
I'm gonna go help Rosa.
Okay, I'm going up to the
scene of the shooting,
and I need your help.
I can't sign tactical
gear out of the armory
without Holt's approval.
That's our mission objective.
First things first. Let's
synchronize our watches.
- These don't work.
- They're just status symbols.
Okay, we'll use our phones,
which are connected to the internet.
I don't get the internet
with my Netscape Blip.
Let's just use the regular clocks.
At 3:34, I'll go into the armory
and hand the officer in
charge a list of items.
Then, at 3:35,
you two will cause a distraction
that draws Holt into the bullpen.
When Holt's not looking,
I'll sneak into the office
and answer the phone
when the armory calls
asking for approval,
fooling them with my
spot-on Holt impression.
"I'm Captain Holt."
Yeah, I don't know, something feels off.
He sounds too white.
Here's how you do it.
No, no, that's okay! Luckily
I have a backup plan.
I got the Holt soundboard app from Gina.
I'm. Raymond. Holt.
Get. Some. Get. Some.
Man, soundboard Holt is so horny.
Anyways, Hitchock and Scully,
to distract the captain,
I'm gonna need you to get in a fight.
- Us? The buddies?
- How would that even work?
You guys are adorable.
But we don't have time for
this, so figure it out!
Okay, so that plumber was useless.
But we are two smart and capable people
who can definitely figure
out how to fix a toilet.
Of course we can.
The internet will tell us what to do.
- She always does.
- Yes!
I'll just search "toilet videos."
Oh! So much porn!
Probably should've been more specific.
"Person fixing broken toilet."
More porn.
How about this? "Instructional video
from a plumber on how to
fix an actual toilet."
Still porn! How is that still porn?
Okay, you know what,
this isn't rocket science.
All right? The first thing we gotta do,
shut off the water supply.
Did I do that?
That's an Urkel reference,
from the show "Family Matters."
Do you remember that?
Hey, there. I want to
check out some gear.
All right.
Okay. Get ready.
- It's showtime.
- What?
Hmm? Oh, I just said... I have Showtime.
- The cable channel.
- Mm. Must be nice.
Scully and Hitchcock are
just looking at each other.
I'm a little worried
they're not gonna be able...
You son of a bitch!
Okay, we're a go.
- Ah!
- Ooh!
Oh, my God, they're in a penis punch 69!
- Ah!
Hey, hey, hey!
What's going on? Why are you fighting?
Well, he punched me in the nuts,
so I punched him in the nuts,
so he punched me in the nuts,
so I punched him in the nuts.
But why? You still haven't told me why.
- Um...
Ooh!
Okay. I just need to
get Holt's approval.
Go for it.
- This. Is. Holt.
- Hey.
It's Officer Wilg at the armory.
I got Peralta here.
He's signing out body
armor and a long gun.
Is he all clear?
Yes. Approved.
Thanks. Oh, hey, Raymond.
Can't wait for you and Kevin
to come over and meet the baby.
We still on for Thursday, right?
Screw. That.
I'm sorry, I thought you
wanted to meet baby Carol.
Her surgery was such a success.
Screw. That. Screw. That.
Get. Some. Good. Bye.
Ah. What a weirdo.
Anyways, thanks for the gun.
Okay.
That should work.
The hose thing was disconnected
from the pipe thing,
so the tub thing wasn't filling.
Now we can just turn this back on.
And test it.
Wait, first, let's say a prayer.
Dear Beyoncé, Solange, Rihanna,
someone cool that's white,
Cardi B, please bless this flush.
A-woman.
Okay.
Ah! It works.
We did it!
Uh, what's that weird noise?
It doesn't sound good.
No, no, no. It sounds fine.
That's totally normal. We fixed it.
Oh, damn.
- Gah!
- Going somewhere?
Fine, yes, you got me.
So how'd you know I was sneaking out?
I got a couple of very
angry texts from Officer Wilg
accusing me of quote unquote
hating my own goddaughter.
How close are you with
Colin from the armory?
Let's focus on the real question.
Why are you disobeying an
order from the commissioner?
I'm clearly the good guy here.
All right? If this was a movie,
no one would be on your side.
You're basically the
guy in "Ghostbusters"
who lets all the ghosts out.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
Exactly. Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna go help Rosa.
How? This isn't a movie.
You're not gonna rush onto the scene
and singlehandedly take
down all the bad guys.
I might. My gun is pretty big.
It barely fits in the car.
Want to be a hero?
You want to actually get something done?
Your friends and colleagues right here
are struggling, and they need you.
I did everything I could.
I tried to distract me
and Charles all day long,
and it didn't work.
They don't need to be distracted.
They need someone to help
them face their fears
and deal with the reality
of the situation.
Okay, great. So why don't you do it?
I tried, but it didn't work.
I'm not particularly
skilled at emotional jabber.
I was hoping you would step up.
And I was hoping to actually do
something valuable like help Rosa.
So are you gonna stand in my way or not?
Okay, I think I got it.
Just have to tighten this here,
and here we go.
Please work.
Come on.
Come on!
Flush, you stupid son of a bitch!
Ah!
Wow. Bitches really do be crazy.
Sorry. We should just give up.
This was such a dumb idea.
Yeah, it would only matter
if we actually thought
Rosa was coming home today.
- We should keep going, right?
- Definitely.
Also, it's fun to watch you
get destroyed by a toilet.
Hello?
You know what,
I'm trying to keep this line open,
so I don't have time for your bull crap.
Good-bye, Mom.
I'm so sorry, how's your penis?
Sore. How's your penis?
- Sore.
- I'm proud of us.
- Still too high.
- Okay. What if I cut myself?
Just to let some of the blood out?
I'm sorry, but I can't
stay here all day.
I have other things to do.
- You a traveling nurse, man.
- Don't big-time me.
I'm sorry. Look, it's been a tough day.
Hey, everyone, I got pizza.
Grab a slice.
Probably gonna be a really long night,
and none of you have eaten anything.
Peralta, why are you back so soon?
Because I wanted to do something.
Hey, guys. How're you holding up?
I mean, not great, but I know
you really don't want to talk about it.
No. We should talk about it.
I'm really scared for Rosa.
Me too.
And it keeps making me
think about my kids.
How do I deal with the fact
that every day I leave for work,
I might not come home?
Man, I don't even know, Terry.
I don't have kids yet,
but I know you love them.
And I feel like that's all
you can really do, right?
I mean, now that I'm getting married,
I keep thinking if
something happens to me,
it'll actually affect someone else.
I'd get over it eventually,
after a lot of therapy.
I was more talking about Amy,
but yes, you too, Charles.
Hey, look at that. 130 over 80.
Back to normal. I can get
out of your hair now.
Nice.
Told you, Andrew.
Terry's in tiptop.
Thanks, Jake.
Captain. I know you don't eat pizza,
but I figured you'd want to be included.
Uh, thank you.
You know what would make a great movie?
One where the hero sits with his friends
and they talk about their emotions.
I know that you're just
being nice right now,
but that would be a terrible movie.
I mean, what would the poster even be?
Just a bunch of people's faces?
Guys. Guys, guys, guys.
They just took both
shooters into custody.
Officers got injured in the action.
They don't say how many.
Call Diaz. Get her cell.
Damn it.
It's still just going to voice mail.
_
Okay. I don't have the
names of the injured officers,
but if Diaz is unharmed,
she should be contacting us shortly.
Or, if her phone is dead,
perhaps she'll be walking out
the elevator at any moment.
Come on, Scully!
You can't be doing stuff like that, man!
I was just making a copy downstairs.
Yeah, well, next time, think.
- About what?
- I don't know!
- Okay, Jake.
- Come on, man. Go easy on him.
- Diaz!
- Rosa!
You're okay! Where'd you come from?
Felt like walking, so I took the stairs.
Also, I thought it'd be
funny to mess with you guys.
Rosa, you know I hate pranks.
- You love pranks.
- I do. I really do.
You did it so good.
Were you guys worried
about me or something?
No.
So what happened? Did they shoot at you?
Were you in the thick of it?
It's been a really tough day.
I just want to get a beer.
I don't feel like getting into it.
Are you sure? Because the journey
I went on today taught me
that sometimes it's best
to talk about things...
- Jake.
- Right. It was a stupid idea.
And Holt told me to do it, so.
Let's just go get a drink
and sit in total silence.
Perfect. First, I gotta go to the can.
Actually, you might want to check out
the ladies' room up here.
Hey, Rosa, it's me, Gina Linetti.
Welcome back.
Me and Amy made a little
surprise for you,
and I think you're gonna
like it very, very much.
Come on, girl.
Ta-da!
You made it sound like
you fixed the toilet.
Yeah, I thought maybe Amy would've
pulled something together
in the two minutes
I stepped outside.
Hey, Gina! Look what I stole
from the Barnes and...
Oh, my God, Rosa! I'm
so happy to see you!
Wait, are you covered in toilet water?
Yes, big-time. But this is happening.
Ugh. Fine.
Kinda feel like I'm lurking.
- Gina, get in here.
- Yay!
Synced and corrected by Pisuly
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net