Hey, Jake,
guess who just called me?
The Jerky Boys. They're back!
No. What?
- No.
D.C. Parlov. He's in town for LegendCon,
and he has a case for us!
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God!
Parlov? Didn't he write
those "Skyfire" books?
I thought he turned out to be a jerk.
Yeah, but ever since Jake
and I saved his life,
he's actually been very nice.
He even sent me a Christmas gift.
A full-scale replica of
the sword of Opadoma.
- Unh!
- Why are you so excited?
You don't care about those stupid books.
I actually did read all
of them in prison.
They are the greatest books I've
ever read, and I've read "Cujo."
Jake and I really bonded over "Skyfire."
- Yeah.
- Watch this.
Favorite moment in the series?
The summoning of Balacastro.
- Second favorite?
- The Scarlet Feast!
- Third favorite?
- When you thought Ka'lar
had been swallowed by the Norolith,
but had just switched armor
with Samling the Betrayer
in the battle of Vorcastle.
Fourth favorite?
Three was plenty. So was zero.
Okay, I can see that
you're skeptical, Rosa,
but how about this: come
with us on the case!
I know you think it's dumb,
but "Skyfire" is actually
very smart and dark and adult.
It's not for nerds at all.
Ooh! On our way there,
should we sing the elvish hunting song?
♪ Sharpen your swords ♪
♪ And string your bows ♪
♪ The beasts have gone away ♪
- Synced and corrected by medvidecek007 -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Whoa, look at this place!
Ooh, they're selling moss wine.
I wonder if it's as gross
as the books say it is.
I can never get into any of this crap.
I think the reason is
because it's garbage.
Rosa, I think if you
just gave it a chance,
you would get hooked.
I mean, what is it that
you do in your free time that's so cool?
Fix up old cars and sell
them to celebrities.
That's why I'm friends with Tom Hardy.
Right, so we agree that
we're all equally cool.
Here we go. This is Parlov's panel.
"Diversity in Fantasy Writing."
Ooh, the line starts here.
Real diverse diversity panel.
And, like, people always ask me,
"Where do you get your ideas?"
And honestly, Wikipedia.
I always try to pull from life.
Queen Tiffany, of
course, was named after
a lovely hostess that I met
in Bonita Springs in Florida.
You know, I've always wanted
to write a book myself,
but all I know about is cops,
and there are literally
no more cop stories to tell. Zero.
- I've actually been writing a novel.
- Wait, what?
You're writing a book? When? For who?
For me... for fun.
Look, I'm not trying to be an author.
I don't even know how
to go about doing that.
Parlov! You should show it to Parlov.
- He could probably get it published.
- No, that's crazy.
Like, I'm sure it's bad. I
don't want to be embarrassed.
Terry, you are a great husband,
father, detective, painter, dancer,
and you're so jacked you
have muscles on your back.
Everyone has back muscles, Jake.
Nuh-huh, my back looks like
the inside of a spoon.
The point is, you're
great at everything.
You're probably great at writing, too.
I am not showing Parlov my book, okay?
All right.
Here he comes. Now just drop it.
Sorry, I hope that wasn't
too tedious for you.
It was fascinating, especially to Terry.
- He's a writer, and he wrote a book.
- Would you read it?
- Dude!
- Sure. Love to, absolutely.
But listen, there's something
I want you to see.
Come with me, guys, all right?
- Jake!
- What?
Terry, you need to believe in yourself,
like when Morzak answered
the sorceress' riddle!
She turned him into a tree, Jake.
Yeah, a tree that became
the handle of Prominius' axe.
Parlov is so far away already.
Yeah, good call. Let's go after him.
Hey.
The desk sergeant said we're hosting
a forensic sciences course.
Yes, taught by Dr. Ronald Yee.
He revolutionized the field
of forensic entomology.
He is a rock star.
Oh, please. Rock stars
wish they were he.
The man can tell how long a
corpse had been decomposing
just by studying the maggots inside.
I'd like to see Barbra
Streisand do that.
I'm not sure Barbra Streisand
counts as a rock star, sir.
She sings in English. That's rock music.
Well, it sounds interesting.
Can I sign up?
Yes, you can,
but here's the thing: if
we do well at this course,
we receive board certification,
which makes us eligible
to receive a grant
to open a field lab in the precinct,
but...
Eh... but whenever we
have a speaker come in,
you kind of tend to always
derail these things
with personal stories.
That's how I learn.
I relate course material
to my experiences.
Subjective learning.
Millennials.
I know it's important, so I promise,
I won't tell any stories,
though sometimes they do come in handy.
One time, all the Boyles were in
this fungus cavern, and this
massive mushroom comes...
- Charles.
- I am so sorry.
I slipped right into it. I'll be good.
This is my room, right over here.
Listen, I need just a
moment to clean up.
I had a female visitor in earlier today
dressed as Concubina.
She got smears of green body
paint all over everything.
Everything.
He was talking about his penis.
- I know, Jake.
- He pulls, Rosa.
- He pulls. That's all I'm saying.
- I can't believe you
- told him about my book.
- I'm sorry, Terry, but now
D.C. Parlov is going to read what
you wrote! How cool is that?
- He's pretty cool.
- Right?
You haven't even told
me what it's about yet.
Well, it's the story
of a Gorgon warrior...
- Awesome.
- Who betrays his bloodline...
- How could he?
- To marry a Cloud Princess...
- He did it for love.
- Even though
- their families are at war.
- No! All right,
no more spoilers. Send it over to me,
and I'm gonna stay up
all night reading it.
- It's only 150 pages.
- I'm gonna stay up
all the next three nights reading it.
Dr. Yee will be here any minute,
and we need to make a good impression.
If you need to cough...
Cough now.
My God, what if I hadn't said anything?
Don't worry, I got this.
Nobody sucks up like a Boyle.
Our scoliosis allows us
to bow more deeply than normal people.
Huh, here's an idea: Santiago
and I will impress him
with the depth of our
forensic knowledge,
and you can wow him
with your stoic, silent demeanor.
No stories. Understood?
Stoic. Ah.
Good morning, everyone.
Thank you for having
me at the Nine-Nine.
Sorry I'm late. Just had to deal
with some family issues.
Cousins, right?
Okay, before we get technical,
let's talk a bit about
the history of blood.
Does anyone here know any hemophiliacs?
So many...
Now, they played a vital role
in the development of modern forensics.
Them and leeches.
My cousin Torvald is a hemophiliac,
and his wife is a leech farmer.
I say "wife," but it's
a common-law marriage.
For the longest time,
Boyle wedding ceremonies
were not recognized in the state.
- _
- Well, here's the situation:
somebody stole my laptop,
which contained the
unpublished manuscript
of book 13 of "The Skyfire Cycle."
The person left this note.
"We have your book.
"Pay us $500,000 in the next 24 hours
"or we leak it online.
"The first five chapters are now up."
They've been downloaded 85,000 times.
Well, we should probably
go online and read those
chapters in case there's
some clues in there,
and also maybe we'll find out
Qwandor's true parentage?
- Oh that's already been revealed.
- No, it hasn't.
Unless the prophecy of Dorgon
is indeed true!
- But that would mean...
- You seem pretty calm for somebody
- whose book was just stolen.
- Because I know who took it.
- Landon Lawson.
- He was on that panel. He writes
"The Shadowbringer Saga." It's garbage.
So why would Lawson want
to steal your manuscript?
We both have books coming out this fall,
and we have a rather public bet
about whose is going to sell better.
I believe he's leaking
my manuscript online
just to hurt my sales.
- You should arrest him.
- Well, we're not going to
do anything until we've
seen all the evidence.
If this book fails,
that's the end of "Skyfire."
Let's go take this son of a bitch down!
Mr. Lawson? NYPD.
Let me guess: you're here
about the stolen manuscript?
So you admit you did it?
Well, that was easy.
What? No. Someone stole my manuscript,
and I know who it was:
D.C. Parlov.
By Zorton's Sword!
It's the exact same note Parlov got.
I don't see why anybody would
want to steal your book.
"The Skyfire Cycle" makes
"The Shadowbringer Saga"
look like "The BeastWorm Chronicles."
You see, Rosa, "The
BeastWorm Chronicles"
are one of the more simplistic...
- Don't care.
- Yeah.
You know what? My books
say something, okay?
I was the only one brave enough
to tackle elf molestation.
Guys, calm down. You're both victims.
Now, do you have any enemies in common?
Let me think about that.
Parlov is my enemy,
but he's also his own enemy,
because he's such a boring
and repetitive writer.
He just keeps killing off characters,
resurrecting them, and
killing 'em off again.
Because of the Chrysalis Orb!
Uh, sorry.
Police officer, on a case.
But we will need you to
both generate actual
lists of people that
might want to hurt you.
We have 24 hours to
figure this out, but if
we don't, are you willing
to pay the ransom?
I'd do anything to get my book back.
I mean, you understand. You're a writer.
Do you hear that, Terry?
He called you a writer.
Terry, did you hear? Terry?
Well, Terry's broken.
Write up those lists. We're on the case.
- _
- Welcome back.
So today, I want to focus on
facial reconstruction.
For over a century,
we used plaster casts
to help identify decomposed
John and Jane Does.
We buried my Nana Boyle
at the family farm,
but because of the soil's
high salt content,
she turned into jerky. Never mind.
- Please continue.
- Now, I need one person per group
to have a plaster cast
made of their head.
Uh, will he... or she...
Be able to speak?
Not while the plaster's on, no.
- I vote Charles.
- Charles.
I was gonna vote me, too.
I mean, I know the plaster
can dry out your skin,
but as a Boyle, I'm aggressively moist.
Oop, you gotta close that mouth, Boyle.
Shh-shh-shh-shh.
Keep still and quiet.
Have you been here all night?
We traded off, and
each slept a few hours
right here in the break
room, but we got a lead.
You know Miles Moorgil?
He wrote "The Nocturine Quartet" novels.
Well, Moorgil is the only person
on both Parlov and Lawson's
lists of potential enemies.
Apparently, they each
slept with his wife.
How do these guys do so well with women?
Oh, I'm sorry they don't live up to
your superficial standards
of male beauty, Rosa.
I'm kidding. It's because they're rich.
Moorgil's here for the conference.
We're gonna go confront him
and get the laptops back.
Then, maybe, we can see if
Parlov read my book yet.
Oh, well, I mean, it's
been less than a day.
- Maybe don't get your hopes up.
- Don't worry.
I don't have any expectations.
- Good.
- I'm gonna be at my phone,
just in case a publisher calls.
I mean, someone.
Yeah. Whatever.
It's fine. My hopes are up.
All right, buddy.
I couldn't sleep last
night, so I started
reading Terry's book, and it's terrible.
I made him show it to Parlov.
He's gonna be humiliated.
Relax. How bad could it be?
So bad, and I'm entertained
by everything.
I once went to a play.
So what are you gonna do about Parlov?
- I don't know.
- Don't know what?
Uh, how to do...
Sex... good.
How much should I be
flapping my arms around?
- Not much.
- Right.
Well, that settles that.
I knew that Amy was wrong.
Anyways, let's get back
on the case, right?
Skyfire Cycle.
Okay, now that the plaster's dry,
you'll see why we lubricated the
subject's face with Vaseline first.
Oh, no, we forgot the lube.
Charles, can you hear us?
What do we do?
Doctor? Uh, what if someone...
No one in this room, mind you...
Forgot to lubricate before
applying the plaster?
Oh, one of my lab techs
made that mistake once.
It becomes impossible to remove the mask
without literally skinning
the subject alive.
It takes five days for the plaster
to slough off on its own.
And what became of the lab tech?
Oh, I fired him. It was an
unacceptable level of incompetence.
Huh, what a satisfying
conclusion to that story.
- Boyle!
- Mm.
A mistake was made and we
can't remove your mask yet.
We're gonna leave you in here...
Until after the class is over,
because if Dr. Yee sees you like this,
we can kiss our certification good-bye.
I'm sorry, Boyle,
but Hitchcock and Scully
will be here with you.
I don't know, Captain.
He seems pretty upset.
- Hold on.
- Mm!
Look how happy he is now.
Yes, you're welcome, Boyle.
I don't understand.
Why do you think I would
steal those laptops?
Parlov and Lawson are your rivals.
You're jealous of their success.
And of course, you have
a personal motive.
You hate them for
sleeping with your wife.
- What? They slept with my wife?
- And you didn't know.
Well, this is awkward. We
should probably just go.
- Jessica!
- She's here.
- That's wonderful.
- Yes, sweets?
Did you sleep with D.C.
Parlov and Landon Lawson?
- Uh...
- Why would you do that?
You've ruined our marriage.
You've ruined it!
You know, this seems like a
conversation for just you two,
so... oop, here comes a child.
Mommy? Daddy?
Are you getting divorced?
Are they getting divorced?
Uh...
Oof.
Okay, that was a rough 70 minutes.
- Yeah, but...
- That kid looked exactly like Parlov?
100%.
Oh...
Anyways, that was our last lead,
so looks like we're back
at the Nil Caverns.
- Did you just say the Nil Caverns?
- Hm?
- Like, from my book?
- Uh, yep.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, I did,
because you told me about them
when you were explaining the plot.
I didn't, but that's because I wanted
the Nil Caverns to be a surprise.
Why didn't you tell me
you read my book, Jake?
- Uh...
- Oh, no.
- You hated it.
- What?
Terry, no, I didn't hate it.
- I liked tons of parts.
- Name one.
Name one part you liked, Jake.
- The map?
- I didn't draw that!
It was a map of the Chesapeake Bay
with the names slightly changed!
Oh, my God.
You made me show Parlov.
You humiliated me in front of my hero!
Sarge, I'm sorry.
Look, I didn't just like the map.
I also liked...
the spaces between the words!
That's not helpful.
You guys got a million dollars
together on 24 hours' notice?
Yeah, I had to liquidate my Bitcoins.
Oh, really?
I would've thought you'd
be flushed with cash
from the "Skyfire" TV series.
Oh, wait, that's right.
The CW passed.
How's the "Shadowbringer"
film coming along?
Howie Long still playing both twins?
All right. Let's go over the plan.
Okay, there's a potted tree on
the east side of the lobby.
They said to leave the
briefcase behind that.
If someone grabs it,
Rosa, Peralta, and I
will converge. We'll be positioned
around the room in disguise.
It's not gonna work. I
don't own a nerd costume.
Oh, but Rosa, you are
already wearing one.
You naturally dress like
the female bounty hunter
in every steampunk novel.
Look. All you need are welding goggles.
Damn it.
I have welding goggles in the car.
Shall we to battle?
To solve that problem, we would
use fluid dynamic analysis.
That is exactly right. Well done.
Where's your friend?
Shouldn't he be here for
the plaster removal?
Something came up, so he
had to remove the mask,
which came off quite
easily, and run out.
It was urgent police business.
Bunch of kids are being held hostage,
so he had to go deal with that.
Oh, well, if you need to leave
to provide him with backup...
- No, it's a teachable moment.
- The children
- can handle themselves.
- Captain Holt?
Your husband's on the phone.
He wants to know how long
you're going to kiss for tonight?
Would you excuse us for one moment?
Your husband didn't really call.
I wasn't sure what gay guys talk about
on the phone. How'd I do?
Scully, what do you want?
We were watching Charles, like you said,
but both of us had to go to
the bathroom really bad.
Ugh. Where's Charles?
- We have no idea.
- What?
- Terry, do you copy?
- I copy.
- Seriously? You're still mad at me?
- All I said was "I copy."
Yeah, but you had a tone. Just admit it.
- Let it go, Jake.
- No, he's right.
Terry had a tone.
- Terry had a big-time tone.
- Don't worry.
I bet he hasn't even read your book yet.
It's been two hours. I'm almost
at the front of this line.
I don't even know who I'm
waiting to take a picture with.
"Bran Stark?" Pass.
Okay, he's just the three-eyed raven.
Here we go, here we go. We got action.
He dresses just like you, Jake.
Is that someone popular?
Yes, Rosa, it's Ka'lar.
17th of his name, sworn
knight of the Queen's Crown,
the Daybreaker, the rightful heir to...
All right. You can just say "Ka'lar."
Uh, then how will you know which
Ka'lar I'm talking about?
It's a very common name in "Skyfire."
It's like their John.
He's going for the briefcase.
Okay, let's go.
Don't make your move
until you're close to him.
There's too many civilians.
Wait, why are there so many Ka'lars?
Costume contest just ended.
That's why he waited until
now to pick up the money.
I lost him. Which one is it?
It's the one headed toward
the service elevator.
Hey! Freeze!
NYPD. Let me see your hands.
What's going on?
Doesn't have the briefcase.
I got the wrong Ka'lar.
- I have eyes on him.
- Take him down!
Wrong Ka'lar...
Boyle's not in the interrogation room.
He couldn't have gotten far.
He can't see.
You can go a long way
on muscle memory alone.
One time, I sleepwalked
- to the M&M's store in Times Square.
- Oh, oh!
Stairwell.
- Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
- I'm okay.
It's okay. Sorry, stranger.
I just can't see anything at all,
and it's really scary being touched.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Just return me to the 99th precinct.
Boyle, it's us.
Where were you going?
Why would you leave
that windowless supply
closet we locked you in?
Ah, yes, hearing it, I understand why.
I was trying to get to the locker room
to steam the mask off in the shower
so you guys could still get certified.
Wait.
You were trying to help us?
Even though you'll be stuck
in this mask for five days?
Five days?
Well, I know how important
the course was to you.
It's not.
Not anymore.
I'm so sorry.
I just cannot see at all.
I can't believe it!
Now I'm out $1/2 million!
What am I supposed to do now?
Write another "Compendium of Beasts"?
Do you have any idea how hard it is
to find enough interns to
slap that crap together?
God!
Don't worry about him.
At least we got to stop that thief
from releasing any more chapters.
All we're out is some
money, plus I've got
insurance, so I'm going
to get it all back.
By the way, Detective Jeffords,
while we were waiting,
I had an opportunity to
read your manuscript.
Oh, don't worry about that.
It's a work in progress.
Has a lot of changes I...
No, no, no, it was great. Truly.
Fantastic. I mean, it
was so fresh, you know?
It had a really unique point of view.
I sent it on to my publishers.
Thank you for allowing me to read it.
And I want to thank you all
for your hard, hard work on this case.
Appreciate it.
Ooh, did you hear that?
He loved it.
D.C. Parlov loved my writing!
You were wrong!
And being wrong never felt so right.
Oh, that sounded cool. Did
I just make up a hit song?
♪ Being wrong never felt so right ♪
♪ With the Addams Family
staying up all night ♪
Yep, I was right. It's a hit.
I gotta go call Sharon!
All righty. Well,
congratulations, Sarge!
And don't forget about us
when you become a famous author.
Terry's writing sucks.
Parlov is lying to him.
- What? Why?
- I don't know.
He's buttering him up...
because Lawson and Parlov
stole their own books!
♪ Well, they stole their own books ♪
♪ It's plain to see ♪
♪ But who's on the case ♪
♪ The Addams Family ♪
♪ Terry is Gomez, I'm Cousin It ♪
♪ You are Wednesday, let's do this ♪
Okay, we should go.
Why do you think these
guys are in it together?
They hate each other. They spent an hour
arguing over the name of the
dragon in "The Hobbit."
- "Smog."
- "Smowg."
- Smog!
- Smowg!
It's "Smowg," by the way...
Point Lawson... but yes,
they're mortal enemies,
which is why they think
we'll never suspect them
of being in cahoots.
Oh, but they cahooted, Rosa.
They cahooted all over us.
Gross. Why'd they leak their chapters?
To get people excited, like when Carly
Rae Jepsen puts out an amazing single,
and you have to wait six weeks
for the album to come out.
She's great. I'm not apologizing.
So Parlov contacted
Terry because he knows
Sarge is a super-fan and
can be manipulated.
Yes, he's been giving Terry
presents since last year.
And Terry's novel gave Parlov
another chance to manipulate him.
Unless...
is it possible Parlov actually
likes Sarge's writing?
Read the first sentence.
- Yep, Parlov did it.
- Very much so.
Gah! Now I have to tell Sarge
that his fantasy novel stinks.
This is the hardest part of being a cop.
Now, there are issues with RFLP testing,
as there are with every
technique, but...
Captain, I thought you said
your friend removed his mask and left.
I forgot to lube up his face.
We failed to listen to the instructions.
That is incredibly careless.
I know, and it means we won't receive
our certification, and
I'm okay with that.
- Unless my honesty...
- No, it's off the table.
- And I'm okay with that.
- Well, anyway, RFLP testing
was designed to localize
genetic disorders, and it...
Ooh, my cousin Donna
has a genetic disorder
where her lips were made of cartilage,
meaning her mouth is technically a beak.
I don't see how that
pertains to anything...
No, let him talk. I want to hear it.
Boyle, tell us about your cousin's beak.
Well, she runs marathons
to raise money for other people
afflicted with "bird-face."
There are only two of them.
- They're her kids.
- Oh, Sarge!
Funny seeing you here.
Oh, that reminds me.
I have to tell you something.
What was it?
Out with it, Peralta.
Okay, fine. Here it goes.
- I think that...
- Parlov hated my book.
He only said he liked it
so I wouldn't figure out
he and Lawson stole
their own manuscripts.
- You figured it out.
- Well, I had a gut feeling,
so I went digging.
I got a warrant for
Parlov's browser history.
He searched "how to liquidate Bitcoins"
three days before the
laptops were stolen.
Man, I bet that browser
history was a nightmare, huh?
- Oh, you have no idea.
- Yeah.
Anyway, I questioned them,
and they confessed.
I can't go to prison, okay?
I know I seem tough, but I'm not.
- I went to Bennington.
- Ew.
I'm sorry Parlov didn't like your book.
And I didn't. And also Rosa.
- Why did I add that?
- No, it's okay.
At least I won't waste any more
time trying to be a writer.
Wait, let me ask you a question.
Are you a better cop now
than when you started?
- Nope.
- Wasn't talking to you.
Yeah. I look back at my old cases
and I can't believe how long
- it took me to figure things out.
- Yeah, but you worked on it,
and you kept working, and now,
12 to 40 years later...
I don't have a good sense of your age...
You're a great cop who
got a "gut feeling"
and solved a huge case.
So you think I should keep writing?
I mean, you might not become
a huge famous author,
but you'll get better,
and if it makes you happy,
it can't be that bad.
Sheryl Crow, she's great.
I won't apologize.
And who knows? Claire Essalgorn
didn't start writing the
first "Crimson Portal" novel
until she was 60.
I started reading it because
the character looks like me.
I kept reading it because it's so good!
Rosa, you did get hooked, you big nerd!
This heroine is my heroin.
Oh, such a dweebus. I love it!
Speaking of which, Parlov's
laptop is in evidence.
Want to go read the new "Skyfire" book?
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, he's such a bad guy.
Do we even like his books anymore?
♪ Sharpen your swords ♪
♪ And string your bows ♪
- Synced and corrected by medvidecek007 -
- www.addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net