- _
- I'll get back to you guys
by the end of the day
with all the logistics.
Sergeant Terrance Jeffords,
four years ago on this exact date,
you told me I was too old
to learn how to do the worm.
I vowed on that day to prove you a fool,
and today, I shall.
Check it.
I'm on fire!
As I was telling the
squad, our old C.O.,
Captain McGintley, just passed away.
Oh, no.
We're going to Los Angeles
for the funeral next week.
I'll have the travel details later.
Hey, has anyone seen a worm?
Because this funky chicken's hungry.
Charles, a man has died. Read the room!
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
- _
- Oh, man. Sad day.
Sad day.
It's crazy how different things were
when McGintley was Captain.
It was like the Wild West.
- Oh, yeah, we had some fun.
- I didn't.
In every one of those photos,
I look uptight and worried.
Meanwhile, everyone else looks like
they're having the time of their life.
That's because they're all stress-free,
not like us Type A's.
Jake, am I too high-strung?
I wouldn't say you're too high-strung.
You just are high-strung.
You know, your strung
is what makes you strung.
- You're strung strongly.
- No, not anymore.
From now on, I'm gonna be super chill.
So, where's the party at?
Trick question. The
party's right here, boy!
Oh, hello, Mrs. McGintley.
My condolences for your loss.
So, who do you got your eye on?
- What?
- You haven't dated anyone
since you broke up with Pimento.
And funerals are a meat market.
Sadness is a powerful aphrodisiac.
- No, it's not.
- Then how come everyone cries during sex?
I'm already seeing somebody, Boyle.
Oh...
And just like that,
things got interesting.
And just like that, I left.
- Hello, Raymond.
- Oh, Chief Aggerton.
I didn't realize you'd
be flying out for this.
I liked McGintley. He was
fun to have a beer with.
There's nobody in this department
I wanna have a beer with anymore.
Yes, that's the problem with the NYPD.
So, I hear you're meeting with
the Commissioner on Monday morning.
Well, you didn't hear this from me,
but Commissioner's retiring next year.
They put a short list together
of possible replacements,
and you're on it.
- This is your first interview.
- Really?
- What?
- Oh, my God.
- What's going on?
- What's going on is
Captain Holt has an interview
to become the Commissioner
of the freakin' NYPD,
and he's gonna nail it
and fulfill his destiny
as Lord High Commander of all Justice.
Okay, let's not get carried away.
Who says I'm even interested
in becoming Commissioner?
You, constantly, including
the first day I met you.
I'm interested in becoming Commissioner.
- Good to know.
- Fair enough, but even so,
it's probably a long shot.
I mean, there are
many names on the list.
Nope, just four.
Yeah, three major league jags and you.
Sir, you're the perfect candidate:
smart, well-respected, you smell great.
That has nothing to do with the job.
It's just something I've
been meaning to tell you.
- Is it sandalwood?
- Please calm down.
Right, totally. Don't wanna jinx it.
I don't believe in jinxes.
Great, then you won't
mind me saying it's a lock.
You're definitely gonna get it,
and you're gonna smell even better
with that Lord High Commander
of all Justice stank on you.
Let's do this
- _
- I can't wait to get on a plane.
I used up my miles, and
upgraded first class.
- Damn, Sarge.
- This is gonna be great.
Sipping on a mimosa,
snacking on a hummus trio,
watching "Bridget Jones's Baby."
- Oh, GPS says turn left here.
- Turn left.
No, this route is more direct.
Oh, okay. You do you, Commish.
- Please don't call me that.
- Okay, fine,
I'll just call you the 'Mish...
no wait, Mishy Elliot...
no wait, Mish-es Doubtfire. Oh, my God!
- What? What is it?
- Nakatomi Plaza.
It's the most important
monument in all of America.
The building from "Die
Hard." Can we go in?
- Can we pay our respects?
- Ooh, our flight leaves in 3 and a half hours, and...
but it's like, what is time even?
#LegalizeIt.
- Can we go in, sir?
- Fine, just make it quick.
Yes! Pull in over there, Argyle!
- What?
- That's the name of the driver in the movie.
We're going to Nakatomi Plaza.
There's gonna be role-play.
Oh, my God.
It's even more beautiful
than I imagined.
It's an empty floor
that's under construction.
Just like in the movie!
Charles, this is the floor that John
McClane ran on with his bare feet.
Take my picture with it!
This is the window
where John McClane said,
"Welcome to the party, pal."
Take my picture with it!
This is the vent where
John McClane said,
"Come out to the coast. We'll
get together, have a few laughs."
Take my picture with it. This
is the space, where even though
it's not really evident in the dialogue,
you can tell that John McClane realizes
that he should've been a better
husband. Take my picture with it!
Take my picture with it!
Take my picture with it! But
then he unclasps the watch,
and Hans falls!
That's a good one. That's a good one,
That's a good one. That's a good one...
That's a good one. Okay,
all 600 of these are great.
- We should probably head to the airport.
- We have more time, if you need it.
There's literally nothing
left for me to shoot.
All right, let's get out of here.
The door is locked.
That's strange, I thought
the guard propped it open.
I'd kick my way out, but I think
these windows are bullet-proof.
We're not getting any reception in here.
Guys, it's cool. We
just gotta roll with it.
- You know, travel should be like jazz.
- Nuh-uh.
There's a lie-flat seat waiting for me,
and I wanna be napping in it,
with a hot towel wrapped
around my big bald head!
- Help!
- All right, everybody just calm down.
I'm sure that guard will be
back in, like, five minutes.
- _
- We're gonna miss our flight.
I should be sitting next
to a semi-famous person
that I can't quite place right now.
Come on, don't give up.
If we get rescued right now
and there's no traffic at the airport
and the van return goes smoothly
and Security's super chill
about all the guns we have,
we could still make it.
- You guys okay up here?
- Yes! See?
I told you not to give
up hope. It's a miracle.
- We're still gonna make it!
- Yeah, we missed our flight by a lot.
Yeah, but that's okay.
We can get the next one.
Let's see, next flight...
Cancelled. Cancelled.
- Cancelled. What is going on?
- There are huge storms in the Midwest.
- All flights are grounded.
- Oh, man.
I know this is the wrong
time to bring it up,
but we're standing 75
feet from where Argyle
picked up John McClane at the airport.
- Take my picture with it.
- Yeah.
Okay, we can't get out until
Monday afternoon, at the earliest.
I tried everything. I begged.
I pleaded. I even told them
that Scully was a Make-a-Wish
kid with a rare disease
that makes him look
like a giant old baby.
- Did you call it Scullyosis?
- Damn it, Rosa,
that's really good and
completely useless to me now.
They wouldn't even let me
into a first class lounge,
since my flight had already departed.
I grabbed this and ran.
You're all that's left of
my dreams now, Mr. Mint.
All right, stop hugging your
mint. We have bigger problems.
Captain Holt's Commissioners
interview is on Monday.
- Can't he just reschedule?
- No!
He's gonna be up against
the best of the best.
The slightest slipup could
cost him the job, and...
but whatever, you know.
It is what it is, Daddy-O.
Look, Captain Holt helped us all achieve
our collective dream of
going to Nakatomi Plaza.
- Only you.
- Now it's time for us
to return the favor and
help him achieve his.
Get him back to New York
in time for that interview.
Now, we have until Monday
morning, and it takes...
48 hours to drive from L.A. to New York.
- We've still got time.
- No, we don't.
I checked with all the
car rental agencies.
There are no available vehicles.
I'm just gonna have to call the
Commissioner, cancel this meeting.
No, not on my watch.
We just have to think. There's
gotta be a way to get you back.
Got it! May I present
to you the finest RV
that not much money can
buy: The American Creeper.
No one should have to
suffer like this for me.
Suffer? This is a dream come true.
It's a cross-country road trip.
My dad and I took one every summer.
You blast the "Annie" soundtrack,
and you eat junk food,
and you bond over secrets.
I'm not telling you who I'm dating.
All right, I'll take the first shift.
American Creepers, let's get creeping!
- _
- Hey, one hour down.
Victory honk.
Oh, no. Oh, boy.
Horn's stuck.
Nobody use the horn.
_
What you got there, Sarge?
I microwaved a bunch of wet
napkins to make a hot towel.
Just because we're in a crappy RV
doesn't mean I still
can't be First Class Terry.
Mmm...
Ah...
Just like the real thing.
_
Cheese puff, sir?
No, thank you. They're
full of chemicals.
Well, yes, but everything's
made with chemicals,
if you really think about it.
- I suppose you're right.
- I am?
- Let me try one.
- Oh.
- It imploded in my mouth.
- That's the magic of the puff.
You don't have to chew.
So, what are you gonna
do when you're Commish?
I think you should focus on interagency
communication and intel sharing.
Also, laser jails.
Let's not talk about
things that may not happen.
Oh, I'd like to see an
increase in vacation days.
And we should all get
summers off like teachers.
- Let the city go to purge.
- _
Hey, Rosa, are you
ready to go streaking?
- What?
- That's what my dad and I called
getting blonde streaks in your hair.
We used to do it to our
ponytails on road trips.
You just take a little lemon up top,
and let the sun do the rest.
We called it giving
each other road head.
You just said you called
it going streaking.
It had a couple names.
Hey, speaking of names...
who's your new boyfriend? Ow! Ow! Oh!
_
Oh, man, you really went to
town on these cheese puffs.
Well, they're 80% air,
which is something your body needs.
Dallas? What the hell? We were
supposed to be in Louisiana by now.
We've been averaging 50 for 21 hours.
Unless...
Damn it! The speedometer's broken.
No wonder everyone was flipping us
off. I thought it was just racism.
- Well, I'm sure it didn't help.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, I don't think
we can make up the time.
No, there's no way I'm letting
you miss that interview.
We just have to make less stops.
Hey, guys, listen up, from now on,
we use the bathroom in the RV.
- No!
- There are so many of us.
- I know, I'm sorry, but it's the only way.
- Me first!
Hey, guys, the door
doesn't close all the way.
No peeking.
_
- You guys didn't hear that, did you?
- I'm still hearing it.
- I'm never gonna stop hearing it!
- Okay, new plan:
we go back to the old
bathroom break schedule,
and we just drive at max speed.
Captain, punch it. Punch it.
- Why are you not punching it?
- I'm not comfortable
operating this vehicle
at a speed greater
than the prevailing road
and traffic conditions.
Fine! I'll do it myself.
This is going great.
I'm already used to the
bouncing and shaking.
- I smell smoke.
- Really?
All I smell is residual Scully.
I definitely smell smoke.
Pull over right now.
Well, I checked everywhere.
Nothing's on fire.
Nothing's even smoldering.
We just wasted ten
minutes for no reason.
You know what, Captain,
I think you're right.
I do smell smoke.
So, bottom-line this thing for me.
How long is it gonna take to fix?
- It's still on fire.
- She's gone, Jakey.
She's creeping her way to heaven.
Let's be honest, she's
creeping her way back to hell.
All right, guys, we have to
focus and think of a new plan
for getting Holt back for his interview.
Now, all we've lost is our
only mode of transportation.
And our clothes and food!
All I have left is
this first class mint,
and none of you get to eat him!
Well, perhaps we should just focus on
finding a place to sleep tonight.
I might have a solution for that.
How far is it to Mansfurd, Texas?
- Like, half an hour.
- Great!
I have cousins there:
Becca, Tommy, and Steve.
- There's a Boyle in every state.
- Texas Boyles. I'm excited.
Do they wear bolo ties and cowboy hats?
Nope, still just beige on tan.
- Steve, Tommy, Becca!
- Becca is a man.
Oh, thank you so much
for letting us stay here.
- I love you.
God, it is so nice to meet you guys!
Is this a working cattle ranch?
Oh, yes. This is a stud farm.
We are the cow insemination
kings of Central Texas.
Of course you are.
We have sleeping bags for you
guys here in the great room.
If you hear what sounds like screaming,
that's just cow intercourse.
Now we're all sleeping in one room,
- next to a cow orgy.
- I would much rather be hanging out with you.
- What are you doing, Boyle?
- Just brushing my hair.
Not you, Becca. I was
talking to Charles.
- I was just bringing you some water.
- Thanks.
Mm-hm. So, uh,
who you talking to? Is
that your mystery hunk?
Babe, are you all right?
Is everything okay?
Yeah, it's fine. I'll
call you back later.
- Was that a woman's voice?
- It's my sister.
Wait... she called you babe.
When my cousin called me babe,
you said relatives shouldn't do that.
What's really going on?
I'm dating a woman.
- I'm bi.
- Oh...
That's great.
That's great, Rose. I just want you
to know that I totally support...
I don't wanna talk
about it right now, okay?
- Just leave it alone, Boyle.
- By all means.
Not you, Becca!
Okay. I love you.
I love you too.
Can't sleep either, huh?
- This cow screaming is so loud.
- So loud.
Is it a pleasure sound or pain?
- Maybe they're into both?
- I hear they're into leather.
- Was that a joke?
- Gallows humor.
Being in this bovine
brothel is truly a nightmare.
Hey, I'm sorry that
things didn't work out.
I know you always hoped
that you'd be Commissioner.
No. Over the course of my career,
I've learned that it's
best not to have hopes.
Sir, that is so sad.
That's like saying it's
best not to have dreams.
I only have one dream a
year, always on Tax Day.
In it, I must file an extension.
So, yes, it is best not to have dreams.
Well, I still wish I
could've got you back in time.
Why do you care so much about this?
I don't know,
it's your dream, and, you know,
you changed my life, made me
wanna be a better man, or whatever.
Thank you for trying.
But deep down,
I always knew I'd never be Commissioner.
All my dreams start with my
step-sister painting her house.
And they end with the
house looking great?
No. Sex.
Guys! Guys! Wake up, wake up, wake up.
- Up, up, up! Come on!
- What's going on?
Captain Holt, I know you've given
up on your future, but I haven't.
- You're going to that interview.
- It's too late, Peralta.
Just put a sock in it, man!
I'm doing this because of
how much I care about you,
so just stay the hell out of the way!
But we're too late to drive,
- and there's no available flights.
- That's what I thought,
but on the way here, we
passed the town of Jacksboro.
I knew I recognized it from somewhere.
Where? Sorry, are you monologuing,
- or is this a call-and-response thing?
- No, that was great.
Now, I order a lot of beef jerky online,
'cause I'm a cool guy
with cool interests,
and it's always shipped
from Jacksboro, Texas.
There's a huge fulfillment center there.
- There is?
- Yes, Charles.
I called them, and
they ship their packages
- out of a regional airport.
- They do?
That's too much. Maybe
back off a little bit.
Passenger planes don't
fly out of Jacksboro,
but thing planes do!
- You mean cargo planes?
- Yes, thank you.
- Terry gets to interject?
- The point is,
we get to fly on the back of
a cargo plane to Philadelphia.
When do we have to be in Jacksboro?
In an hour and a half,
so get up and get ready.
Well, we've been in these clothes
since Friday. We smell like butt.
- And all our stuff exploded.
- Right, good point.
Uh, I guess we'll just
have to borrow some.
Oh, no. From who?
We look so cool right now.
I feel like we're in
a Mervyn's commercial.
Yeah, Mervyn's!
Is this cattle trailer safe?
Who cares, it's fun.
Yeah, it's terrifying,
but it doesn't matter, because
we're almost to the airport.
What? No, why?
Just because we're eight people
standing in the back of a cattle car?
Nah, I don't care about that.
We got a tip saying there
were drugs being moved
in the back of a gray
bovine transport unit.
Well, this is terrible.
Wait a minute, who called this tip in?
- It's impossible to say.
- They said the drugs were
in the back of a bovine transport unit.
- Who calls it that?
- Everyone. That's what they're called.
Yeah, if you're a robot,
and you're the only robot I know, sir.
Bovine. Transport. Unit.
- Meep-morp. Zeep.
- This is preposterous.
- What are you implying?
- Let me see your phone.
- I wanna see your call history.
- No.
- Let me see it!
- No...
- no! Get away!
- Give it to me!
Guys, come on. Break it up!
Ah-ha!
25 minutes ago, outgoing call to 911.
You sabotaged us, Mr. Robot!
Not the TV show, but the
point is, you sabotaged us!
Terry, would you do the honors?
Why?
You called the pigs on us?
I don't know how this happened.
- Perhaps it was a bottom dial.
- Liar.
The reason you said you knew
you'd never become Commissioner
is 'cause you were making sure of it.
You've been sabotaging
us from the beginning.
Oh, please.
You drove by Nakatomi Plaza
on purpose, didn't you?
You knew I would see it and go
insane and have to go inside,
and then you trapped
us in there, didn't you?
- Didn't you?
- Fine. I did.
Over here is the elevator where McClane
put the "now I have a
machine gun, ho, ho, ho" down.
Take my picture with it!
And there were plenty of rental
cars at the airport, weren't there?
- Hundreds.
- And you broke the speedometer. And what else?
Did you somehow force
Scully to stink up the RV
- so we'd have to stop more often?
- It wasn't difficult.
Three corndogs for 99 cents?
Who could possibly eat three
corndogs and has a dollar?
Oh, my God.
- Did you blow up the Creeper?
- Not on purpose.
Once I realized your
revolting cheese puffs
were made with some
extremely unstable chemicals,
I deposited a few in the gas tank.
I thought they'd shut the engine down.
I didn't realize they'd ignite it.
- You really shouldn't eat those, Peralta.
- Don't tell me what to do, saboteur.
How dare you make me this upset
while I'm wearing this outfit?
Look, we've been busting
our asses the whole weekend
to try and get you back to
New York in time, and for what?
Is it all just a lie?
Is there even a Commissioners
meeting. Are you even Captain Holt?
- Do you even have a dog named Cheddar?
- There's a Commissioners meeting,
and I do have a dog named Cheddar.
Then why'd you do it?
I'm compromised.
I made a decision a while ago,
and now some people are
holding it over my head.
I'm afraid of what they'll ask
me to do if I become Commissioner.
You're compromised?
How did this happen, Mr. Prevailing
Traffic and Road Conditions?
It doesn't matter.
Seamus Murphy.
- What?
- Seamus Murphy, the gangster.
He offered me info that would
get you and Rosa out of prison,
in exchange for a favor.
And Holt told me to turn it down,
because he said it was too risky.
But you didn't turn it
down, did you, Captain?
No, I did not.
- Wait...
- So you risked everything
to get me and Rosa out of prison?
Oh, my God. You did all of this for us?
I love you, Da... aptain... Daptain.
It's the cool new way of saying Captain.
It's from the world
of hip-hop. Love you.
Sir, why didn't you tell us?
I didn't want any of
you entangled in this.
This is my decision,
and it's also my responsibility.
Sir,
with all due respect,
the first thing that you taught me
when you came to the
Nine-Nine is that we're a team,
so your responsibility
is my responsibility too.
- And mine.
And mine.
Six people seems like a
lot. I mean, at some point,
it's just too many cooks.
- And mine.
- You're gonna take that meeting,
you're gonna get the job, and
you're gonna become Commissioner,
and we'll all figure out
what to do about Murphy.
I'm touched...
But it's moved. We've
missed the cargo plane.
And now there's no
way to get back in time
- for me to make my meeting.
- Nuh-uh.
- Amy?
- What up, bro?
I need you to climb back
on that strungness ladder,
and I need you to climb pretty high.
- How high?
- Remember that time
we went to the deli for cold cuts,
and the ticket machine was broken,
so you found out what
time everyone arrived
and made them get in a single-file line
- from earliest to latest?
- Yeah.
Higher.
Copy that.
You might wanna stand
back for this, sir.
It can get pretty intense.
All right, you mooks,
our union health plan
has 100% reimbursement for
out-of-state ambulance rides.
Scully will fake a medical emergency.
Don't need to fake it.
Always having at least one.
Great. You call an ambulance,
and have it take us here
to Monroe, Louisiana.
The ambulance can drive 25 miles
over the posted speed limit,
so we'll get there by 9:00 p.m.
There's a small airport there,
mostly servicing crop dusters.
Of course, they can't take passengers,
but thanks to a loophole in H.R. 377551,
police officers are allowed
to commandeer any plane
in the interest of national security.
The crop duster will land at an airstrip
outside of Finksburg, Maryland.
We'll take a cab to Baltimore,
jump on the 6:48 a.m. train to New York,
arriving at 9:26.
Kevin will meet us at Penn Station
with a fresh Captain's uniform.
From there, it's a 29-minute
cab ride to One Police Plaza.
You change on the way, and
we should get to your meeting
with five minutes to spare.
Stop clapping, you idiots!
We gotta move, move, move!
I love her.
_
Yes! We did it!
I can't believe we did it!
Peralta, thank you
for not quitting on me.
Of course, sir. Go get 'em.
Wait, wait! Just one more thing.
Your first class mint?
I know how important this is to you.
You know what really
makes a trip first class?
It's not the extra leg room
- or the complimentary drinks...
- Actually, Terry,
we don't really have time
for a speech right now.
Fine, your breath sucks!
Just pop it and go!
It's good to be home.
Uh-buh-buh-buh-buh!
- Drink this instead.
- A mimosa!
Made with First Class Champagne.
That's the brand name.
It's from Arkansas.
I hope it's good.
- Hell yeah!
- Really?
No, it's terrible, but I
really appreciate the thought.
Oh, I'll take it.
- Hey.
So, I didn't say
anything about being bi,
because I didn't think
it was anybody's business.
And I also didn't want
anything to change.
I get it. I'm sorry I was so nosy.
It actually felt really good to
tell somebody on the squad, finally.
- I'm glad it was you.
- All right.
Also, now we go back to never
talking about my love life again.
Uh, request denied. Is her
name Anne? Meredith? Kim?
- Erica? Moana?
- Captain Holt!
It's official. My hat is in
the ring for Commissioner.
I still don't know how
we're gonna deal with the
- Murphy complication.
- Two words: laser jails.
- But, you know, we'll figure it out.
- Nine-Nine!
Nine-Nine!
Not a doctor.
www.tvsubtitles.net